实在很难没发现
So...couldn't help but notice
你们全都没如约出席我的神秘谋杀周一夜派对
none of you RSVP'd to my murder mystery dinner party.
对哦
Oh, yeah.
我们正打算去呢
We were meaning to do that.
放屁  派对是上周的事了
No, you weren't, because it was a week ago
你们全都没来
and nobody came!
想知道是谁以"毫不在乎"为刃
So, if you want to solve the mystery of who stabbed
从背后捅死了库萨帕里的这个谜团吗
Koothrappali in the back with the weapon of indifference,
凶手就是你们
it was all of you.
这应该不算是个谜团吧
I don't think that qualifies as a mystery.
我们早知道是我们干的了
We all knew what we were doing.
实在很抱歉  拉杰什
We're sorry, Rajesh.
说不定我们下周再约一次啊
Maybe we can do it next week.
我们也没这么抱歉吧
Whoa, whoa, we're not that sorry.
不用啦  我懂你们的意思
Don't worry, I can take a hint.
不会再办神秘谋杀游戏派对了
No more murder mystery parties.
-谢谢  -感谢老天
- Thank you. - Hallelujah.
因为我计划好了更棒的活动
Because I've got something even better planned.
-为啥啊  -不是吧
- Aw! Why? - Come on.
先听我说嘛
Just hear me out.
我计划给你们办一场
I'm going to make you guys
麻省理工学院式的寻宝游戏
a scavenger hunt like they have at M.I.T.
我以前很爱玩呢
I loved those.
每年都去参加
I did them every year there.
我们普林斯顿大学也有呢
We did them at Princeton, too.
傻孩子  那学校算哪门子大学啊
Oh, that's cute. Like it's a real college.
真有意思  我本来也打算这么说麻省理工的
That's amusing-- I was going to say that about M.I.T.,
不过拿去说普林斯顿大学也行
but it works for Princeton, too.
哈佛大学的寻宝游戏很有挑战性
Scavenger hunts at Harvard were really tough.
我总是在第一个关卡就卡住了
I always got stuck on the first challenge--
就是找到人愿意跟我组队的关卡
trying to find someone to be on a team with me.
看来这故事是"好惨"不是"好笑"
I guess that story's more sad than funny.
我也爱寻宝游戏
I love scavenger hunts.
我以前常跟朋友一起玩
My friends and I had them all the time.
我们玩的应该有些差别
Oh, these are a little different.
这是在精英大学里...
There's a tradition at elite universities.
以及普林斯顿大学
And Princeton.
这寻宝游戏  内含无数谜题
A tradition of hunts full of puzzles
得靠逻辑  晦涩知识与科学来取胜
that rely on logic and obscure knowledge, science.
我们的寻宝游戏  就是到处找
Oh, in ours we would just run around town
愿意卖啤酒给未成年的店
looking for a store that would sell us beer.
谁要来玩
So, uh, who's in?
-我觉得听起来挺好玩啊  -我也觉得
- I think it sounds fun. - Yeah, me, too.
-我参加  -来吧
- I'm in. - Let's do it.
抱歉  我们是真要参加呢
I'm sorry. Are we really doing this
还是只是像上次派对那样
or are we tricking Koothrappali again
只是哄库萨帕里玩而已
like with the dinner party?
人人影视
YYeTs.com
翻译：狂躁妮妮赛太公  分心艾咪YY猫
翻译：累赘佩妮坏小泡  淡定耳朵醉芝士
生活大爆炸
第七季  第三集
这些是干啥的
What's all this?
寻宝游戏中
Oh, everything I could possibly need
我可能会用到的东西
to win the scavenger hunt.
你真觉得他会让我们去保龄球馆吗
You really think he's gonna send us to a bowling alley?
如果真发生了
Well, if he does,
你知道球馆里的球有多脏吗
do you know how filthy those rental balls are?
其程度不亚于去街角
They might as well stand on the corner
帮人做免费的直肠指检
and give away free rectal exams.
好了  各位
Okay, everybody.
谁准备好要参加...
Who's ready for a...
寻宝游戏
scavenger hunt...?
本市的
Somewhere...
某一个地点
in the city of Pasadena,
我藏了一枚金币
I've hidden a golden coin.
你们一共需要解出
You will be faced with a total
10道谜题
of ten puzzles!
每道
Each p...
每...
Each...
每道谜题将带领你
each puzzle will lead you
到下一个指定地点
to the location of the next.
而最后的谜题
The last of which
将会指引你找到金币
will lead you to the coin.
第一个找到金币的队伍就
The first team that finds it...
赢了
wins!
他真是个天生的主持人
He is a born showman.
有问题吗
Any questions?
有  为了确保公平
Yes, to be fair,
是不是该让普林斯顿大学的先出发
do people who went to Princeton get a head start?
不好笑好吗
That's not funny.
如果你懂笑点就好笑了
Oh, it actually is if you get the joke.
这笑话是以
It's based on the premise
嘲讽普林斯顿是间烂学校为笑点
that Princeton isn't a very good school.
笑死人了
Ha-ha.
你们看  他懂笑点了
Oh, see? Now he gets it.
好了  大家
Okay, guys, go ahead
你们先选人组队  两人一组
and divide yourselves into teams of two.
我们要不就与各自伴侣吧
Should we just do couples?
情侣一组不错
Couples sounds great.
或者我们可以混合一下
Or we could mix things up.
抽签决定跟谁一队吧
Maybe pick names out of a hat.
都行啦
Whatever.
你干嘛不直接承认
Why don't you just admit
你不想跟我一队就好了
you don't want to be on a team with me.
我刚也说"情侣一组不错"啦
I just said, "couples sound great."
你就是觉得我不够聪明
Yeah, you don't think I'm smart enough.
你觉得我会是"千钧重负"
You think I'm gonna be a liability.
就算我刚刚才正确使用了
Even though I totally just used
"千钧重负"这个词  也还是不够
the word "liability" correctly in a sentence.
没错
Yeah.
那就情侣组队吧
All right, let's-let's do couples.
我想跟你一队
I want to.
别  别  晚了
No, no, no.
大家就混合一下
Let's mix things up.
我选跟谢尔顿组队  我们会让你输得一败涂地
I choose Sheldon, and we're gonna kick your ass!
非得选我吗
Yeah... really?
我第一次被人首选选入队
The only time I'm ever picked first for a team
结果却是跟"千钧重负"一队
and I'm stuck with the liability?
别这么说  佩妮才不是呢
Stop that. Penny is not a liability.
谢谢  你想跟我一队吗
Thank you. Do you want to be on my team?
我们还是抽签决定吧
Maybe we pick names out of a hat.
快点过来  然后把门关上
All right, hurry up and close the door
这样他们才听不到我们说话
so they can't hear us.
可以别不甘心地扁嘴了吗
Would you stop pouting?
是说你自己抽中了我名字
So, you picked my name.
乖乖接受这事实吧
Get over it.
好的  你知道我抽中你名字的
Yes, and do you know what the odds are
-几率是多少吗  -不知道
- I'd pick your name? - No.
不难啊  五分之一嘛
It's not hard-- one in five.
现在你知道我为什么扁嘴了
Now you know why I'm pouting.
所有队伍听好
All right, teams.
准备打开你们第一道谜题吧
Get ready to open your first puzzle.
开始
Go!
瞧我多有哏
Do you see what I did?
第一道谜题就是拼图[谜题]
The first puzzle is a puzzle!
天啊  我真是太佩服我自己了
Oh, my God, how adorable is that?
真希望有一个像我一样的朋友
I wish I had a friend like me.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你得先从边缘开始
You have to start with the edges.
拼图没有正确的方式  谢尔顿
Well, there's no right way, Sheldon.
我已经拼好了几块了
I already found a few pieces that fit.
那就拆了  然后从边缘开始拼
Yeah, well, take them apart and start with the edges.
不要浪费时间了
And stop wasting time.
你拼图真厉害
Wow, you're really good at puzzles.
我小时候经常玩拼图
I did them all the time as a kid.
我妈以前常跟我说
As my mom used to say,
"当你在玩拼图时
"When you're doing a puzzle,
就像有成千上百个好友在跟你一起玩"
it's like having a thousand friends."
那时的她  总是爱说善意的谎言
She was full of fun lies like that.
如果能让你好过点
If it makes you feel any better,
我小时候我妈总是在吃大蛋糕
my mom's just full of pound cake.
抱歉你得跟我组队
I'm sorry you got stuck with me.
我猜你一定想跟伯纳黛特一起
I bet you wanted to be with Bernadette.
-你有跟伯纳黛特玩过游戏吗  -没有
- Have you ever played a game with Bernadette? - No.
感觉就跟和狼獾一起关在铁笼子里一样
Have you ever gone into a steel cage with a wolverine?
快点  快点  快点
Faster, faster, faster!
你懂那个词的意思吗
Do you not know that word?
快点就是"加快一点"
It means "more fast"!
别对我大声嚷嚷
Stop yelling at me.
喂
Hey!
现在老娘还不算在嚷你呢
You'll know when I'm yelling at you.
我知道了  是漫画书店
Ooh, ooh, it's the comic book store!
好了  快走吧
All right, come on.
那是我们下一个目的地
That's where we have to go.
但我们拼图没拼完呢
But we haven't finished the puzzle.
那有什么关系啊
Well, it-it doesn't matter!
我们都知道答案了  快走吧
We know the answer! Come on.
是你觉得你知道答案了
You think you know the answer.
但这可能是陷阱
But it could be a trick.
万一等拼图拼完
What if when the puzzle's complete,
我们发现图中有个窗户示意我们
there's a sign in the window that says,
"去小火车商店"呢
"Go to the train store"?
肯定不会这样的
Okay, it's not gonna say that.
我希望你是错的
Well, I hope you're wrong.
因为我真的很想去小火车商店
I really want to go to the train store.
是漫画书店
It's the comic book store.
快走
Let's go!
快点  笨蛋
Come on, numb nuts,
是漫画书店
it's the comic book store!
漫画书店  是漫画书店
It's the comic book store, it's the comic book store,
就是漫画书商店啦
it's the comic book store!
果然是漫画书商店
It's the comic book store.
你觉得佩妮在生我的气吗
Do you think Penny's mad at me?
因为你行驶在右侧车道
Because you're in the right lane behind a bus
又不敢超巴士的车吗
and you won't go around it?
她肯定觉得遵守交规很迷人
I'm sure she finds it charming.
不  是因为我不想跟她组队
No, because I didn't want her on my team.
我倒是觉得她逃过了一劫
I'm starting to think she dodged a bullet.
世上最龟速最难熬的一劫
The slowest bullet in the world.
我从来不知道你好胜心这么强
Geez, I never realized you were so competitive.
对啊  我懂你意思
Yeah, I know.
可能是因为我有
It's-it's probably because I grew up
五个兄弟姐妹
with five brothers and sisters
所以我每次都得跟他们争
so I had to fight for every...
天啊  你刚居然因为一只鸟减速了
Oh, my God, you did not just slow down for a bird!
你知道它们会飞走的吧
You know they fly, right?!
我觉得这是我们第一次
I think this is the first time we've ever
真正意义上的独处
actually been alone together.
你说得对
Huh, I guess you're right.
为什么会这样呢
Wonder why that is?
我第一个想到的就是
Well, off the top of my head,
我们没什么共同点
I'd say we don't have a lot in common
除了因为各自伴侣  所以朋友圈有了交集
except for the people we're involved with.
而且我们第一次见面时
Plus, when we first met,
佩妮告诫过我  千万不要单独跟你一起坐车
Penny warned me never to get into a car alone with you.
说的没错
Yeah.
我觉得我们的共同点肯定比想象中要多
You know, I bet you and I have more in common than we think.
比如说
Such as?
我也不知道
I don't know.
告诉我你喜欢什么
Tell me some things you like.
我想想
Uh, let's see.
我喜欢竖琴  《草原上的小木屋》
I like harps, Little House on the Prairie,
中古时期的诗歌和文学
medieval poetry, medieval literature...
不如我们来听点音乐
Hey, how about some music?
好呀
Great.
谢尔顿就从来不让我在车里听音乐
Sheldon never lets me listen to music in the car.
他不想被人误会是黑帮成员
He doesn't want to be mistaken for a gang member.
挑你喜欢的听吧
Find something you like.
披头士  太无聊
Beatles, boring.
阿姆  太吓人
Eminem, scary.
怪人奥尔
Weird Al?
你几岁啦
How old are you?
尼尔·戴蒙德
Neil Diamond?
我喜欢尼尔·戴蒙德
Yeah, I love Neil Diamond.
我超爱尼尔·戴蒙德
I love Neil Diamond.
* 卡洛琳  小甜心 *
* Sweet Caroline *
* 欢乐的时光从未如此美妙 *
* Good times never seemed so good *
* 美妙  太美  太妙了 *
* So good, so good, so good *
* 我一直以来 *
* I've been... *
谢谢让我借用你的漫画书商店
Oh, hey, thanks for letting me use the comic book store
作为我寻宝游戏的藏迷地点
as part of the scavenger hunt.
乐意之至
Oh, my pleasure.
我总是很乐于帮助一些
Always happy to help out with fun things
从来不邀请我参加的娱乐活动
that I wasn't invited to be a part of.
恭喜你们
Oh, congratulations.
你们是第一组到达的队伍
You're the first team to arrive.
太棒了  这不是整我的诡计
Yes! It's not a ruse to make fun of me.
这是真的游戏  而且我领先呢
It's a real game and I'm winning it!
你们下一道谜题是猜谜语
Your next puzzle is a riddle.
谁最适合给人出谜语呢
And who better to give it to you
肯定是非谜语人莫属啦
than The Riddler?
蝙蝠侠对手中第一个智慧型罪犯  每当他犯下案件后
总是会刻意留下谜语线索来玩弄蝙蝠侠还有警察
快  快  快  快
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
你怎么会跑得这么比我还慢
How am I faster than you?
亏老娘穿着高跟鞋  半路还停下来接电话呢
I'm wearing heels and I stopped to take a phone call.
我有哮喘好吗
I have asthma.
不许再催我
Back off!
"猜一猜"
"Riddle me this.
"阿拉  阿拉  聚集在一起"
"Arrah, Arrah, and gather round,
"这个英雄是军团成员"
The work of this hero is legion-bound.
"他用N乘以He的数字"
He multiplies N by the number of He,
"就在此房所见的它山之石中"
and in this room the thing you'll see."
-谜语不错吧  -是啊
- Good riddle, huh? - Yeah.
所以你们这群人每次玩好玩的
So when you guys plan fun activities,
就没有想到过
does my name even...
我的名字吗
come up, or...?
我邀请你参加我的神秘谋杀派对了
I invited you to my murder mystery party.
你没有
No, you didn't.
我们是最后一个到的  快点
We're the last ones here, hurry up!
这是马拉松  不是短跑
It is a marathon, not a sprint.
马拉松也是用跑的啊
People run in a marathon!
他们又没背着保龄球跑
Not with a bowling ball on their back.
佩妮  我想祝你好运
Hey, Penny, I just wanted to say good luck,
希望你心里不会不高兴
and I hope there's no hard feelings.
喂  罗密欧
Hey, Romeo!
想修复感情  麻烦用你自己的时间
Repair your relationship on your own time.
别紧张嘛  这谜语这么难
Relax, it's a hard puzzle.
解开是需要一点时间的
It's gonna take a while to solve.
-"猜一猜"  -我知道了
- "Riddle me this..." - Got it.
瞧啊  普林斯顿
Hey, Princeton, look at that,
社区大学夜校队领先啦
Team Community College Night School is in the lead.
我们不是闪电鲨鱼队吗
I thought we were the Lightning Sharks.
这个的意思可能是
Hey, you know what this could mean...
很好
Oh, oh, that's good.
那这个就是
Then this would be...
就是这个
That's it.
回我们的"尼尔"战车
To the Neil Mobile!
我就知道我们会输的
I knew it, we're gonna lose!
等一下  我知道了  我知道了
Wait, I got it. I got it!
恭喜你  "最后一个"想出来了
Congratulations, you got it last.
你知道你超级毒舌吗
You're really mean, you know that?
所以最后也没人要买东西
So no one's gonna buy anything.
好的
Okay...
瞧瞧看
Let's see.
"要想继续你们的探索
"To continue on your quest,
就要翻个水落石出"
leave no stone unturned."
下一条线索可能在这里的
The next clue must be hidden
某个"石"头下面
under one of these rocks.
好的
Oh. Okay.
谢尔顿  我很好奇
Sheldon, I-I've got to ask.
你怎么知道答案是地质实验室的
How did you figure out that it was the geology lab?
简单
Oh, simple.
谜语中"阿拉  阿拉"代表震·阿拉
The "Arrah, Arrah" In the riddle meant Jan Arrah,
他是"超级英雄军团"的成员
a member of the Legion of Superheroes,
也就是元素小子
known as Element Lad.
然后"He"这个词[他]
And then the word "He,"
不是代表男性的名词
it wasn't the masculine pronoun,
而是"H-E"
but rather, "H-E,"
是氦的简写
the abbreviation for helium.
明白我的思路了吗
See where I'm going with this?
明白
Yes.
少装蒜了
Nice try.
元素小子的能力
Now, Element Lad's ability
是让化学元素变质
is the power to transmute chemical elements.
而氦的原子序数是2
Helium has an atomic number of two.
如果你用2乘以N的原子序数
If you multiply that by the atomic number of "N"--
N是氮
nitrogen--
就是14  而14是什么的原子序数呢
you get 14, which is the atomic number of...?
我就知道你不懂  是硅
I'm just funnin' you, silicon.
而硅是地表最常见的元素
And that is the most common element in the Earth's surface.
因此范围就缩小至
So that narrowed it down
地质实验室  或化学实验室
to the geology lab or the chemistry lab.
我可以在水下喝啤酒哦
I can drink a beer underwater.
我肯定你的父母以你为傲
And I'm sure your parents are proud.
最后
Now, finally,
谜语说"就在此房所见的它山之石"
the line "in this room the thing you'll see"
明显是在指
was an obvious reference
与"它"同字的神奇四侠的成员"石"头人
to Fantastic Four member The Thing,
他是由什么东西造的呢
who's made entirely of...
闭嘴
Shut up.
我想到了
I solved it.
这是地图坐标
Those are map coordinates.
知道了  我们走
Got 'em. Let's go.
等一下
Well, wait.
你不想知道我是怎么想到的吗
D-Don't you want to know how I figured it out?
没人喜欢显摆自己博学的人  佩妮
No one likes a know-it-all, Penny.
* 在船上  在飞机上*
* On the boats and on the planes *
* 他们要来美利坚 *
* They're coming to America *
* 从此不再回头 *
* Never looking back again *
* 他们要来美利坚 *
* They're coming to America *
你开我的车  我没意见
Um, I'm okay with you driving my car.
但你能不能别玩漂移呀
I'm not okay with you flying my car.
别紧张兮兮的  我老爸是警察
Don't sweat it, my dad's a cop.
出事了他会搞定
He can fix things.
他能起死回生吗
Like death?
你的孩子或许是优等生
Your kid may be an honor student
可你是个蠢货
but you're a moron!
佩妮没回我的短信
Penny's not answering my texts.
随便啦  专心比赛
Who cares? Focus on the game.
她就是因为这傻了吧唧的比赛才生我的气
This stupid game is why she's mad in the first place.
-我要告诉她我退出  -不行
- I'm telling her I'm quitting. - No!
你不能做  退出游戏
Quitting would be the worst thing
-会伤害你们感情的  -为什么
- for your relationship. - Why?
这样你就真的成了
Because it would make you seem like
她认为你是的那种人了
something she already thinks you are.
她觉得我是哪种人
What does she think I am?
我该怎么说呢
How do I put this?
她一直在背后给你起外号
She's been known to call you a name
通常是用于称呼女性私密部位
that usually applies to a lady part.
或者是猫
Or a cat.
pussy  有女性阴部  小猫
银柳以及孬种  娘娘腔的含义
或者柳树的词
Or a willow.
真不敢相信她会那样说我
I can't believe she would say that about me.
你要是想哭的话
If you're gonna cry about it
我的包里有纸巾
there's tissues in my purse.
你自己包里要有也行啦
Unless you got some in yours.
"大银柳"
Big willow.
* 他们要来美利坚 *
* They're coming to America *
* 就在今天 *
* Today *
* Today! *
-好了  往前30英尺  -好
- Okay... another 30 feet. - Okay.
是保龄球馆呢
It's a bowling alley.
万岁
Yes.
Yes!
朕是全世界最聪明的人
My brain is better than everybody's!
* 爱情触礁 *
* Love on the rocks *
*并不意外 *
* Ain't no big surprise *
* 给我倒杯酒 *
* Just pour me a drink *
* 我会告诉你一些谎言 *
* And I'll tell you some lies... *
居然说我娘炮
Call me a lady part.
老子要用行动去证明
We'll see about that.
你能看见迷题吗
Can you reach the clue?
差不多了
Almost.
快点  谢尔顿和佩妮
Hurry, Sheldon and Penny
在保龄球馆时就在我们后面
were right behind us in the bowling alley.
看到了
Got it!
太棒了  爬上来
Great, climb back up.
爬啊
Come on!
佩妮说的话也不是完全没有道理
Yeah, Penny might be onto something.
去天文馆
To the planetarium!
出发
Let's go!
去拉布雷亚沥青坑[洛杉矶考古遗址]
To the tar pits!
出发
Let's go!
下个月有尼尔·戴蒙德的演唱会
There's a Neil Diamond concert next month!
去吧[出发]
Let's go!
三个袋子  没人打开
Three bags, no one's opened 'em.
我们是最先到的
We're the first ones here!
这袋是脏衣服  给你
It's dirty laundry. You're up.
为什么是我
Why me?
你为此做了一辈子的训练准备
Because you've been training for this your whole life.
你生活在一堆脏衣服之中
You live in a pile of dirty laundry.
他们先到了
They're here first.
都怪你逼我为那个盲人减速让路
This is because you made me slow down for that blind guy.
线索肯定在袋子里
Okay, the clue must be in the bag.
The clue must be in the bag.
只是一堆裤子
What's... it's just a bunch of pants.
It's just a bunch of pants.
我很意外你居然抄袭我的答案
You know, I'm surprised you want to copy my answers
毕竟我蠢到根本不配和你一组
since I'm not even smart enough to be on your team.
你为什么想和我一组
Well, why would you want to be on someone's team
你不是管我叫...
who you like to call a...
这词我都不敢当着谢尔顿的面说
I can't even say it in front of Sheldon.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你心知肚明
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
不  她不知道
No, she doesn't.
我瞎掰的
I just made that up.
你为什么要这样做
Why would you do that?
因为你想退出  就像一个大...
Because you were about to quit like a big--
谢尔顿  捂住耳朵
Sheldon, cover your ears.
我不是小孩子了
I'm not a child.
我知道"笨笨"这个词
I know the word "ninny."
你应该退出
Yeah, well, you should have quit
因为我会让你输得一败涂地
'cause I'm still gonna beat your ass.
有个像她一样的女汉子和我一组就好了
Wish I had a man like her on my team.
我从头到脚
Hey, I-I am every bit
都和佩妮一样有爷们气概  好吗
as much of a man as Penny.
开工吧
Now, let's do this!
慢着  不全是裤子  还有件T恤
Wait, it's not all pants, there's one shirt.
这是我的T恤
Hey, that's my shirt.
这件也是
This one is, too.
不  那件不是我的
No, no, that's not mine.
上面有一大块污点
That has a big spot on it.
慢着
But wait.
这件也一样
So does this one.
也许这个污点是线索
Maybe the spot's the clue.
谢尔顿的专座[污点]
"Sheldon's spot."
金币在你专座那里
The coin is in your spot!
-真聪明  -那就快点啊
- Oh, that's clever. - Hurry!
我马上就来
Be there in a minute.
我得把脏T恤先泡一下
I just have to pre-soak these!
拦住她  莱纳德  拦住她
Stop her, Leonard! Stop her!
那金币他娘的上哪去了
Well, where the hell's the coin?
难道答案不是谢尔顿的专座吗
Wasn't the answer Sheldon's spot?
是的  莱纳德
Oh, yes, Leonard.
答案完全正确
Yes, it was.
那金币在哪里
Then where's the coin?
问得太好了
Yes, exactly.
金币在哪里呢
Where is the coin?
你们为什么不看看自己的口袋呢
Why don't you look in your pockets?
我今天早些时候悄悄放进去的
I slipped them in there earlier today.
我不明白
I don't get it.
你还不明白吗
Don't you see?
大家一起玩得很开心时
When we're all having fun together,
每个人都是赢家
we're already winners.
看
Oh, look.
瞧
See?
就连我也是赢家
Even I'm a winner.
你是不是玩儿我呢
Are you kidding me?
这是我听过最傻逼的事
That is the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
你真是烂到爆了
You suck so hard.
我以为
Well, I thought...
拜托  我不希望任何人
Come on, I didn't want anyone
在游戏结束时  因为输了而难过
to feel bad at the end of the game.
有些谜题真的很难
And some of those puzzles were really hard
我不知道谁会倒霉得和佩妮一组啊
and I didn't know who was gonna get Penny.
滚
Run.
好吧  这话是我说得不好
Okay, okay, that-that came out wrong,
但你们得承认
but you have to admit,
游戏过程你们都很开心啊
you all had a wonderful time.
快滚回印度躲着
Run to India.
人家只是想做件令人感动的事
I just wanted to do something beautiful!
你们看
Hey, look.
我赢了
I won.
* 她有办法感动我  雪莉 *
* Hey, she got the way to move me. Cherry *
* 她有办法诱惑我 *
* She got the way to groove me *
* 雪莉  宝贝 *
* Cherry, baby *
* 她有办法感动我 *
* She got the way to move me *
* 她有办法诱惑我 *
* She got the way to groove me *
* 她有办法感动我 *
* She got the way to move me *
* 雪莉 *
* Cherry *
* 她有办法诱惑我 *
* She got the way to groove me. *